海南。整二零二一年初中学业水平考试英语听力。一听句子选图画，看图听句子，选出与句子意思一致的图画。每个句子读一遍。
1. I love my parents.
I have a happy family.
2. Tom loves music.
He often plays the violin on weekends.
3. Eating more vegetables is good for our health.
4. When you have a toothache, you should go to the dentist.
5. Pandas are so popular that they become a symbol of China.
二，听句子选答语。根据你所听到的句子，选出正确的答语。每个句子读两遍。
6. What is your favorite subject?
7. How much is your new dictionary?
8. I am hungry.
Let's get some dumplings.
9. Remember to bring your own bag when you go shopping.
10. Do you mind if I open the door?
三、对话理解：根据你所听到的对话内容，选出能回答所提问题的最佳选项。每段对话读两遍。
Tony, have you finished your science report?
12. Mary. I'm still working on it.
I need help from my sister Tina.
She's really good at science.
13. Lucky you.
Er, is that Tina over there?
14. You mean the girl with long black hair?
No, my sister has black hair too, but it's much shorter than that.
15. right. there is Tina.
She's standing next to the girl with blonde hair.
16. Hey, Tony, have you finished your science report?
17. No, Mary.
I'm still working on it.
I need help from my sister Tina.
She's really good at science.
18. No, Mary.
Tina. She's would you like to go shopping with me this Saturday afternoon?
第二段对话。
I'm afraid I can't.
I will have a swimming class at that time.
Ah, it's important to learn how to swim.
When did you start to learn it?
22. Last month.
It's a little bit tiring but really useful.
23. How often do you have the class?
24. Every Saturday afternoon.
Then, as for the shopping, how about this Sunday?
26. Let me see.
In the morning, I will clean my room, and in the afternoon.
Oh yes, this Sunday afternoon will be okay.
27. Nancy, would you like to go shopping with me this Saturday afternoon?
I'm afraid I can't.
I will have a swimming class at that time.
29. Ah, it's important to learn how to swim.
When did you start to learn it?
30. Last month.
It's a little bit tiring but really useful.
31. How often do you have the class?
32. Every Saturday afternoon.
33. as for the shopping, how about this Sunday?
34. Let me see.
In the morning, I will clean my room, and in the afternoon.
Oh yes, this Sunday afternoon will be okay.
四，短文理解：根据你所听到的短文内容，选出最佳选项。短文读两遍。
Hi, Bill, this is Maria.
I went to your home after school but you were not in.
Here is the final information about the graduation party.
I've booked the restaurant from 6.30 in the evening.
You need to get there at around 6.15, so that we'll have time to prepare before the
guests arrive at 7 o
Are you still okay to get the music ready?
I think pop music will be better than country music or jazz for the party.
As for food, I know we've talked about serving hot food, but I think people will be
happier to have some ice cream after dinner.
Betty is bringing cakes and I'm happy to buy some drinks.
If you have any questions, please call me or Mr.
Black, the restaurant manager, at 6433627.
Bye. Hi, Bill, this is Maria.
I went to your home after school but you were not in.
Here is the final information about the graduation party.
I've booked the restaurant from 6.30 in the evening.
You need to get there at around 6.15, so that we'll have time to prepare before the
guests arrive at 7 o 'clock.
Are you still okay to get the music ready?
I think pop music will be better than country music or jazz for the party.
As for food, I know we've talked about serving hot food, but I think people will be
happier to have some ice cream after dinner.
Betty is bringing cakes and I'm happy to buy some drinks.
If you have any questions, please call me or Mr.
the restaurant manager, at 6433627.
Bye. Thank you for watching.
听力测试到此结束。